Let me tell you the sequence of Chaar Ka Chauka.
Shivangi will come to you. We will have
FN Superstar from Rajesh Palvi for the cheaper option today.
After that, Gab Sir is ready for Chaat Ka
Miracle and Midcap Funda from Narendra Solanki.
But before that,
let's bring Divi's Labs once. That was Palve ji's quick
singles. Let's revisit that trade once after the market opens this morning.
After that, we will start with Chaar Ka Chauka.
Palve ji, I think your first
target is probably getting ready to be hit
or it might have already been hit. I don't know what to
do here now. So
almost now there are ₹3840 left in the target.
We had suggested the first target, so if
you are trading around that, then
definitely book some profit because the market
is volatile. But if you look at it, there is
definitely some strength in the pharma pack. We
feel that if the market stabilizes a bit, if
Nifty stabilizes, then there will definitely be
an outperformance in pharma. So for once,
those who have taken it from an intraday point of view,
then almost now it is trading around the target.
So book some profit there.
You get it back in the dip
around 3800, so we will revisit there and
trade again because of the overall
strength. Okay, so book partial profit
because target one was almost hit.
Target one was also hit here. So for this,
you can book some partial profit
in a Palveji trade.
Now let's start the four-for-four. Then
Shivangi, tell me your cheap option
trade. For the absolutely cheap option,
I have chosen Doctor Ready. You know,
in such a market, when you are taking a pause, there is a
full possibility of pharma of course playing out.
Yesterday we saw that
this stock has shown an increase with a good price volume surge.
Today, a very strong
follow is also visible. So,
here my opinion would be that we should
look for buying opportunities. Buy the call option of 6350.
We can expect it with a stop loss of 135 and for the target of 180.
Okay, so 6350.  Let's take a call
which is around 152 and it
can show levels up to 180, this will
work as a target for you, Doctor Dee's buy side
Rajesh Pal Fin
Superstar, so yes, in the insurance space,
our focus is on ICICI GI, this stock is
General Insurance, so there is stability in this stock
and the way we
see in this volatile market also, the
stock is seen trading on the higher side, the
overall structure is bullish, so it is
advisable to buy ICICI GI here, we are expecting an upside target
in this stock, which can come
around 1670 to 1680, this stock can be
seen moving up, we will keep the stop loss
around 1620, ok Gaba sir, tell me the
miracle of the chart, it will be a miracle of the chart, Axis Bank
breakout has been found, it is trading at 1059,
stop will be
1055, target on the upside is seen at 1070,
in Axis a trade is being
formed towards bullishness, towards 1070 1080
Increasing trade of this counter buy side Narendra
Solanki, tell me what is the
funda, today our funda is
from the IT space, the name of the company is Latent Future
Analytics and if you talk about the results of the company, then the
company has given very good
results and on the margin front the
company has also surprised, the
operating margin has increased from almost 2.4 and the
main reason for this was the investment of the company
in the past to increase the operating leverage, the
company has got a lot of profit there
and in the coming days, if you
look at the guidance, the target of the company
in the medium term is the quarterly
run rate, that is to achieve $25 million
with a margin of 24. And if
you look at the performance of the company in the past eight quarters, then
in the six quarters the company has
decently outpaced the industry growth,
so our target in this is 85,
you can buy it,
for the long term the
target is 585, from a long term perspective, the
latent view, I am recapping all those trades for you.
If you have missed something,
you can also note that. Cheap option:
Advice to take a call on Daughter Reddy's 6350.
When we talked, it was at 152, it has come to 165. The
target has been given for 180. Shivangi
must place a stop loss of 135. Rajesh Palvia
likes ICS Lombard.
This is an opportunity for bullishness for 1670. Then further
target 1680 and
definitely place a stop loss at 1620. Gava Saheb is
saying that there is an opportunity for bullishness in Access. The
target is 1070. Stop loss has to be placed around 1055.
Also,
Narendra ji is giving a buy call on Mitak Funda on the latent view, where he feels that
levels up to 585 will be seen. Let
me show you a couple of counters on the situation screen for you, where a
little momentum has been seen. One is a
healthcare company of the global cash market,
Kani, but this is the same company of
Medanta Hospital.  Momentum has been seen,
this is I beg your pardon, that is
global health, I am talking about health care global,
where a little
momentum is coming, in fact it has become a
part of MSCI index, so some
action is taking place there, in MSTC also a
little action is taking place in that respect, let us tell you that the
views given on Money Control are the
personal views of the experts, the website or the
management is not responsible for it,
Money Control advises the users to take the advice of a
certified expert before taking any investment decision